# Each open ended question is a dictionary, containing three items:
# question: (str) Question Text
# answer: (str) The correct answer. Case Insensitive.

questions = [
    {"question": "Grumpy is an SUTD animal. What is he?", "answer": "Cat"},
    {
        "question": "Where was SUTD's temporary campus before the Upper Changi Campus opened?",
        "answer": "Dover",
    },
    {
        "question": "A giant pokemon sculpture used to sit in various places in SUTD. Which pokemon?",
        "answer": "Snorlax",
    },
    {
        "question": "How many ceiling fans are there in the campus centre?",
        "answer": "5",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the establishment that used to occupy D'star Bistro?",
        "answer": "Cake Shop",
    },
    {
        "question": "The direct underground entrance to Upper Changi MRT (beside Crooked Cooks) opened in the year:",
        "answer": "2019",
    },
    {"question": "When did SUTD end its collaboration with MIT?", "answer": "2017"},
    {
        "question": """The "Chinese Structure" in hostel grounds is donated by a famous movie actor:""",
        "answer": "Jackie Chan",
    },
    {
        "question": "In the old days freshmore students used to build cannons to launch projectiles into NUS as part of their physics 1D project. What projectile was fired?",
        "answer": "Potato",
    },
    {
        "question": """In outreach workshops, the Office of Marketing often sells the "hacker culture" in SUTD by showing a historical photograph of students placing a certain object on the root. What was it?""",
        "answer": "Police Car",
    },
    { 
        "question": "What is the official font of SUTD?",
        "answer": "Gotham",
    },
]
